<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UnityFund</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="enter_full_name">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="have_an_account">Have an Account</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t Have an account?</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="appointment">Appointment</string>
    <string name="my_payment">My Payment</string>
    <string name="rating_and_feedback">Rating and Feedback</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="create_n_account">CREATE \nACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="login_to_your_account">Login to Your Account</string>
    <string name="App_name">UnityFund</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter Your Password</string>
    <string name="continue_with">Continue With</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="all_transaction">All Transaction</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="city_name">city name</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="ngo1">Friends Care Foundation is a Non Governmental Organization established under Society Registration Act, 1860 and The Bombay Public Trust Act, 1950. Organization mainly aims in benefiting underprivileged children and their families through various projects on healthcare, education, nutrition, shelter, livelihood, women empowerment, child protection, and other social issues. Friends Care Foundation’s aims sustainable development by improving social-economic conditions through healthcare, vocational training, education, livelihood development, self governance and women as well as children’s human rights. Friends Care Foundation is dedicated to create positive transformation &amp; believes in bottom up approach. Fostering a society wherein women are empowered enough to add value to their family and society; all children are empowered with education and enjoy their childhood rights, and creating sustainable and humane society wherein all living being have access to manage their livelihood. Friends Care Foundation is focused in Orphanage Support, Child Rights, Education Support, Old Age Support, Women Empowerment, Calamity Relief, Medical Support, Care Of Birds &amp; Animals and Events in Gujarat.</string>
    <string name="ngo2">Omkar Foundation Trust” was established in the year of 2014 by inspiration of Mantrayug Parivartak Saint Shree OmRushi Priteshbhai, considerately known as “Guruji” by his followers. He can deeply understand the difficulties of physically challenged person as he suffered by his own. And that instinct motivated him to do something for this community, consequently by his own inspiration, he instigate trust for elevation of physically and mentally challenged people. He is also engaged with many other social activities for growth &amp; development educationally &amp; financially backward people especially women and children.
Trust is having its office at Ahmedabad, Gujarat. Our team is comprising of 5 other trustees and all are dedicated to our mission and are enthusiastically working towards establishment of the physically and mentally challenged people under blessings of pujya gurudev.
Trust is conducting various activities for physically &amp; mentally challenged people like insurance protection, educational classes, craft works, communication techniques, medical aid, facilitate government aid for such community.
The trust is engaged in different activities like education, social &amp; medical services , skill development etc. Trust is frequently organizing various medical camp like general medical checkups, Allopathic, Homeopathic consultation, blood donation, food distribution for poor and needy people.
Our aim made achievable through donation and contributions received from various organizations and individuals.</string>
    <string name="ngo3">Manav Kartavya would like to ask you, “Have you ever wondered what kartavya a Manav shall does?” Manav Kartavya has not only wondered, but explored it to experience it! Manav has the hands to perform his kartavya by helping others. Manav has the feet to perform his kartavya by hastening to poor and needy. And Manav has the head to perform his kartavya by considering everyone as inclusive to uplift an individual from his state of neediness to a state of self-reliant.
Founded in 2015, Manav Kartavya is an Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India, based Non-Governmental Organization (NGO) committed to helping disadvantaged beings. Each day represents a fresh opportunity to share our Vision of creating, ‘The Advantaged Society’; and to live our purpose of empowering the possibilities for economically weaker communities by supporting them with basic necessities such as education, food, health, shelter, etc. to empower them to take charge of their own future as our Mission.</string>

</resources>