<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UnityFund</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="enter_full_name">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="have_an_account">Have an Account</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t Have an account?</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="appointment">Appointment</string>
    <string name="my_payment">My Payment</string>
    <string name="rating_and_feedback">Rating and Feedback</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="create_n_account">CREATE \nACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="login_to_your_account">Login to Your Account</string>
    <string name="App_name">UnityFund</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter Your Password</string>
    <string name="continue_with">Continue With</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="all_transaction">All Transaction</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="city_name">city name</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="ngo1">Friends Care Foundation is a Non Governmental Organization established under Society Registration Act, 1860 and The Bombay Public Trust Act, 1950. Organization mainly aims in benefiting underprivileged children and their families through various projects on healthcare, education, nutrition, shelter, livelihood, women empowerment, child protection, and other social issues. Friends Care Foundation’s aims sustainable development by improving social-economic conditions through healthcare, vocational training, education, livelihood development, self governance and women as well as children’s human rights. Friends Care Foundation is dedicated to create positive transformation &amp; believes in bottom up approach. Fostering a society wherein women are empowered enough to add value to their family and society; all children are empowered with education and enjoy their childhood rights, and creating sustainable and humane society wherein all living being have access to manage their livelihood. Friends Care Foundation is focused in Orphanage Support, Child Rights, Education Support, Old Age Support, Women Empowerment, Calamity Relief, Medical Support, Care Of Birds &amp; Animals and Events in Gujarat.</string>
    <string name="ngo2">Omkar Foundation Trust” was established in the year of 2014 by inspiration of Mantrayug Parivartak Saint Shree OmRushi Priteshbhai, considerately known as “Guruji” by his followers. He can deeply understand the difficulties of physically challenged person as he suffered by his own. And that instinct motivated him to do something for this community, consequently by his own inspiration, he instigate trust for elevation of physically and mentally challenged people. He is also engaged with many other social activities for growth &amp; development educationally &amp; financially backward people especially women and children.
Trust is having its office at Ahmedabad, Gujarat. Our team is comprising of 5 other trustees and all are dedicated to our mission and are enthusiastically working towards establishment of the physically and mentally challenged people under blessings of pujya gurudev.
Trust is conducting various activities for physically &amp; mentally challenged people like insurance protection, educational classes, craft works, communication techniques, medical aid, facilitate government aid for such community.
The trust is engaged in different activities like education, social &amp; medical services , skill development etc. Trust is frequently organizing various medical camp like general medical checkups, Allopathic, Homeopathic consultation, blood donation, food distribution for poor and needy people.
Our aim made achievable through donation and contributions received from various organizations and individuals.</string>
    <string name="ngo3">Manav Kartavya would like to ask you, “Have you ever wondered what kartavya a Manav shall does?” Manav Kartavya has not only wondered, but explored it to experience it! Manav has the hands to perform his kartavya by helping others. Manav has the feet to perform his kartavya by hastening to poor and needy. And Manav has the head to perform his kartavya by considering everyone as inclusive to uplift an individual from his state of neediness to a state of self-reliant.
Founded in 2015, Manav Kartavya is an Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India, based Non-Governmental Organization (NGO) committed to helping disadvantaged beings. Each day represents a fresh opportunity to share our Vision of creating, ‘The Advantaged Society’; and to live our purpose of empowering the possibilities for economically weaker communities by supporting them with basic necessities such as education, food, health, shelter, etc. to empower them to take charge of their own future as our Mission.
    Manav Kartavya strongly believes that a better, more sustainable world will take shape when economically weaker communities will be equipped with basic needs and proper resources to sustain their lives and to grow. With this, they will gain the power to help themselves, their families, and so to the entire communities. This is what will lead the transformation and will create ‘The Advantaged Society.’
With restoring a sense of self worth and confidence in economically weaker communities, Manav Kartavya is empowering possibilities for every disadvantaged being to reach their full potential. Manav Kartavya is enabling Child Education by improving access to basic educational needs as well as by facilitating education itself; Women Empowerment by supporting the growth from stagnation to escalation through a variety of means; Health by making vital healthcare accessible as well as by spreading awareness about essential preventive healthcare; senior citizens’ shelter and old age related facilities via Old Age Home; and a step forward to help Needy People especially where fundamental economic household security is a big challenge.
Manav Kartavya is not just a committed NGO for helping only underprivileged human beings, but also an NGO which focuses upon enhancing the protection of lives which are of course living beings but not human one. Yes! Manav Kartavya is also an equally committed NGO for the basic protection and enhancement of lives of Gaumatas via Gaushalas.</string>
    <string name="all_ngos">All NGOs</string>
    <string name="our_work">Our Work</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="event">EVENT</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="donation_name">Help someone who need better places</string>
    <string name="ngo_name">By Humankind</string>
    <string name="donate_now">Donate Now</string>
    <string name="raised_100000">Raised: ₹100000</string>
    <string name="read_more">Read More</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.1</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_content">
        Welcome to UnityFund! These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of the UnityFund Mobile Application.
        By accessing this application, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use UnityFund if you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
        License
        Unless otherwise stated, UnityFund and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on UnityFund. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from UnityFund for your personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.
        Restrictions
        You are specifically restricted from all of the following:
        Publishing any UnityFund material in any other media
        Selling, sublicensing, and/or otherwise commercializing any UnityFund material
        Publicly performing and/or showing any UnityFund material
        Using UnityFund in any way that is or may be damaging to the app
        Your Content
        In these terms and conditions, "Your Content" shall mean any audio, video, text, images, or other material you choose to display on UnityFund. By displaying Your Content, you grant our ngos a non-exclusive, worldwide irrevocable, sub-licensable license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate, and distribute it in any and all media.
        No warranties
        UnityFund is provided "as is," with all faults, and our ngos makes no express or implied representations or warranties of any kind related to this application or the materials contained on this application.
        Limitation of liability
        In no event shall our ngos or its suppliers be liable for any damages arising out of the use or inability to use UnityFund.
        Indemnification
        You hereby indemnify to the fullest extent our ngos from and against any and/or all liabilities, costs, demands, causes of action, damages, and expenses arising in any way related to your breach of any of the provisions of these terms.
        Severability
        If any provision of these terms is found to be invalid under any applicable law, such provisions shall be deleted without affecting the remaining provisions herein.
        Variation of Terms
        UnityFund is permitted to revise these terms at any time as it sees fit, and by using UnityFund you are expected to review these terms regularly.
        Governing Law &amp; Jurisdiction
        These terms will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of India, and you submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located in Ahmedabad for the resolution of any disputes.
    </string>
    <string name="appointment_reason">Appointment Reason</string>
    <string name="appointment_title">Appointment Title</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select Date</string>
    <string name="select_time">Select Time</string>
    <string name="save_appointment">Save Appointment</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="contact_support">Contact Support</string>
    <string name="blog_image_description">Image of blog\n</string>
    <string name="blog1">Old age home In early ages, we have seen how vridhasram in Ahmedabad were in bad condition. Let it be in real or in movies, they have portrayed the NGO in a very bad way which gave us a wrong picture of the reality. Today if you pick up the best old age homes in Ahmedabad, there are so nicely built for the elderly with all the facilities and services. They are changing for the betterment of the old aged to cherish their second innings of life. These are now the modern old age homes of India, a heavenly place with the best accommodation, a park to walk and get fresh air, games to play, healthy discussions, funny talks and so on where they would not feel left out, unlike their actual homes.The NGO working for needy people not only take care of the elderly but also provide services to kids who have been treated badly either due to poor family conditions or if it was a girl child. These NGO’s teach them how to become strong and survive in this world. Women empowerment is one of the services provided by the best NGO’s. Some NRI citizens live in these old age homes and they are given special services or provided special features like Video Conferencing, traditional meals, and supported living. They can stay connected to their children in foreign countries and feel better. All these make them feel a heavenly place as they get importance which they never received in their house by their children.NGO in Ahmedabad makes sure that they have required medicines available and proper care is taken to every individual in that old age home. The staff is trained to be courteous and humble towards them and treat them as their parents. They like to sit and talk to the staff for long but one has to make sure that they do not go back to the horrifying picture of how they were abandoned by their children. One day picnics, various activities like entertainment, healing sessions, and some laughter can be held to keep them busy.NGO that helps every underprivileged and old age people need help from people are many in the city that are changing into modern homes with a thought of making it even better than before in the way of living and services to offer.
</string>
    <string name="blog2">In the heart of Surat district, nestled amidst the verdant landscapes, lies the village of Pinjrat. Home to 86 families, this village is located next to a water stream, with its inhabitants primarily depending on agriculture for their livelihood. For years, they relied on a diesel-powered irrigation system, a method that was not only costly but also environmentally unfriendly.

The farmers often found themselves without access to the diesel-powered irrigation system, forcing them to pay extra and rely on outside help to irrigate their fields. The arduous 10 km walk to fetch water from the stream was a daily ordeal. There were times when they couldn’t even set up irrigation for their crops, leading to reduced output and income.

Compelled to seek alternative employment opportunities, such as manual labour, to supplement their income and fund their irrigation system, the farmers eventually reached a point where they could no longer afford to operate the diesel motor pump.

In 2020, CARE India, with the support of Shell India Pvt Ltd, initiated a solar lift irrigation programme after learning about these issues at the annual meeting. The organisations were already working in the area to improve agricultural methods.
    An exposure visit was organised for these farmers to the Dundhi village in the Kheda district, where a similar system was already in operation. The visit helped them understand the economic and environmental benefits of the system.

Excited by the project, representatives from 96 homes in Pinjrat formed the &quot;Sichai Samiti,” a Solar User Group (SUG) that would install and maintain the solar lift irrigation system. To ensure the success of this technical installation, farmers received assistance with administrative facilities and small loans, as this system required initial investment.

The results were transformative. Farmers who used solar irrigation paid INR 36,675 instead of INR 4,51,200 for three irrigations throughout one crop cycle, saving a total of INR 4,14,525. The solar-powered lift irrigation system also reduced travel time, as each farm was connected with pipelines.

The new system ensures that farmers in Pinjrat can grow vegetables even in summer and winter seasons when water becomes scarce. “By saving money, we have also saved time which we spend on other activities. It has enabled us to spend more time with our families and enhance our incomes,” remarked the farmers who benefited from the initiative.
    </string>
    <string name="blog3">Amidst India’s ongoing endeavors to provide education to its young ones, notable non-governmental organizations (NGOs) have been actively engaged in facilitating child education across various regions of the nation. One such commendable initiative is spearheaded by Shaksham Foundation, an NGO for child education in Ahmedabad, steadfastly championing this noble cause throughout the years. It’s worth noting that a staggering 40% of the country’s populace is under the age of 18, constituting the largest child population globally, numbering at a monumental 400 million. The prevalence of poverty and a lack of awareness stands as formidable obstacles contributing to the pervasive issue of illiteracy. Consequently, there arises a pressing need for the younger generation and affluent strata of society to rally behind these NGOs. You, too, can contribute to this laudable endeavor by extending your support to the organization through donations or by engaging in other forms of assistance.

Foundation’s vision is to serve humans with a humane approach. Education, Health, and Healing are our core focus through which Society and nation can prosper in a better and sustained way.

The key priorities of Shaksham Foundation include:

Enhancing quality of education
Enhancing access to education
Shaksham Foundation organizes awareness programmes on the need and benefits of education. Education enhances one’s knowledge. Education is one of the methods of eliminating poverty as it creates independence of thought and develops a perspective of looking at life.

In the pursuit of aiding vulnerable and disadvantaged children, this collective has undertaken numerous initiatives. Renowned as a leading NGO championing child education in Ahmedabad, their approach is characterized by a focused utilization of resources. Explore the core realms of their impactful endeavors below:

Integrating specialization on teaching methodologies
Supporting the professional development of the teacher
Optimizing the use of material, financial and human resources to enhance the qualitative aspects of child education
Shaksham Foundation is also helping the illiterate parents to admit their children in the municipal school and is determined to build a world in which every child attains the right to survival, protection, development and participation. We are currently working Gyaspur, Vatva, Sabarmati locations of Ahmedabad areas where we are currently working for children educational support.

Hence, by extending active support to the NGO or contributing to a noble cause, you directly assist children, their families, dedicated teachers, and other community members responsible for their well-being. The organization allocates these funds towards enhancing educational infrastructure, providing training, offering diverse forms of assistance, and delivering essential services to underprivileged children. It’s important to acknowledge that Shaksham Foundation channels these contributions for the following purposes:

Training teachers, child care providers and principals
Midday meals
Celebrations and exposure visits
Arranging camps for free medical check-ups
Buying learning and teaching materials, like textbooks, teaching manuals, maps, writing supplies, globes, chalkboards and so on.
In the heart of Ahmedabad, where hope meets opportunity, Shaksham Foundation stands as a beacon for child education. Our mission? To sculpt a vibrant tapestry of learning, where every child’s potential blooms. Join hands with us, as we pave the way for a brighter tomorrow through your invaluable support.

</string>
    <string name="blog4">
        The COVID-19 pandemic and extreme poverty have added to the challenges female students’ face living in a predominantly patriarchal society. One of the impacts is on menstruating girls. Menstrual absorbents are essential for self-respect, physical and psychosocial wellbeing. Lack of access to menstrual absorbents causes girls to miss school. They feel embarrassed going to school during their periods. And use unhygienic materials such as rags instead of pads.

Dignity kits are means of providing protection, wellbeing, mobility and hygiene for menstruating girls. Periods do not stop for the pandemic. School-aged girls face a shortage of menstrual absorbents as schools, the only supply chain for many, are shut.
        Recognising “period poverty” as a problem, KHUSHII is helping girls maintain their dignity, safety and hygiene by providing them with “dignity kits” comprising essential items. Along with the ‘Dignity Kits, ‘ KHUSHII also imparts education on menstruation to school-going girls who are approaching puberty. So far, KHUSHII has delivered over 800 dignity kits to girls in two government schools in Mumbai and Rewari. The ‘Dignity Kits’ provide all the required sanitary items, including sanitary napkins, soap, hand towel, toothbrush etc., a total of 17 essential items.

        “Girls in my class appreciate KHUSHII’s interventions such as the distribution of dignity kits and sessions on menstrual hygiene. You have helped restore our dignity. We are now able to and get out of our house during menstruation. Please continue to support us.” – Kirti, a student from Petit Municipal school, Bandra.
    </string>

    <string name="blog5">"
                Join i2u Social Foundation as it celebrates the power of women-led NGOs in revolutionizing human development.
        Women have been a driving force of change since centuries. From Jyotibha Phule to Mother Teresa, they have brought about revolutionary changes in society.
        Being one of the key stakeholders, who are often adversely impacted the most by various social issues, it makes sense when they want to rein in the chariot of social revolution.
        This is why the rise of women-led NGOs doesn't come as a shocking surprise. These organizations, spearheaded by compassionate and empathetic women, are tackling societal challenges head-on, leaving an indelible mark on communities worldwide.
        Through innovative programs and unwavering dedication, they are redefining the landscape of social activism and paving the way for a more inclusive and equitable society.
        The Uniqueness Of Women-Led NGOs
        Women have long been recognized for their innate capacity for empathy and nurturing. These are the qualities that uniquely position them as catalysts for social change.
        As founders and leaders of NGOs, women bring a holistic approach to addressing complex issues, leveraging their deep understanding of human suffering and resilience. Their ability to empathize with marginalized communities enables them to develop effective solutions that resonate on a personal level. This builds a strong foundation of trust and collaboration.
        The transformative impact of women-led NGOs is evident across various sectors, from healthcare and education to human rights and environmental conservation. By prioritizing inclusivity and empowerment, these organizations are not only addressing immediate needs but also laying the groundwork for sustainable change.
        Women leaders, driven by a sense of purpose and empathy, are bridging divides, amplifying marginalized voices, and inspiring collective action.
        Through this article, i2u Social Foundation (an NGO support ecosystem builder) wants to introduce you to some of these amazing women-led NGOs that are working on the ground level.
        Re-Life Foundation: Rebuilding Lives Affected by Addiction
        Re-Life Foundation, under the leadership of V Hemalatha, stands as a beacon of hope for individuals and families grappling with addiction. Hemalatha's personal journey of loss and resilience fuels the foundation's mission to provide comprehensive support and rehabilitation services. Through its intensive in-house treatment programs, Re-Life Foundation offers a holistic approach to recovery, addressing the physical, emotional, and social aspects of addiction.
        One of the foundation's key strengths lies in its emphasis on family-centered care. Recognizing the profound impact of addiction on familial relationships, Re-Life Foundation provides counseling and support services not only to individuals struggling with addiction but also to their loved ones. By fostering a supportive and nurturing environment, the foundation helps families heal and rebuild their lives together.
        In addition to its treatment programs, Re-Life Foundation is committed to raising awareness about the dangers of addiction and promoting preventive measures. Through educational initiatives and community outreach efforts, the foundation strives to empower individuals with the knowledge and resources needed to make informed decisions about substance use.
        Astha Shakti: Nurturing Future Leaders through Education and Empowerment
        Under the visionary leadership of T.G. Aruna, Astha Shakti is making a profound impact on the lives of underprivileged children through its innovative Nutri-Ed program. Aruna's commitment to education and empowerment has led to the establishment of libraries and vocational training initiatives. This is instrumental in providing children with essential resources for success.
        The Nutri-Ed program, a flagship initiative of Astha Shakti, aims to address the multifaceted challenges faced by underprivileged children. This includes malnutrition, lack of access to education, and limited opportunities for skill development.
        By providing nutritious meals, educational resources, and vocational training, the program equips children with the tools they need to thrive academically, socially, and economically.
        One of the program's key strengths is its emphasis on holistic development. In addition to academic instruction, children enrolled in the Nutri-Ed program participate in enrichment activities such as spoken English classes, karate, yoga, and educational trips. These activities not only enhance their academic skills but also foster creativity, critical thinking, and confidence.
                Prayas Samiti: Promoting Early Childhood Education in Rural Communitie

        Inspired by her interactions with rural children during the pandemic, the founder of Prayas Samiti embarked on a mission to promote early childhood education through community libraries. By providing access to quality resources, the organization is nurturing a love for learning and literacy among children in rural areas.
        The Library Project, a pilot initiative of Prayas Samiti, aims to address the lack of educational resources in rural communities and empower children with the gift of knowledge. Through storytelling sessions, art activities, and interactive learning experiences, the organization creates a stimulating environment where children can explore, discover, and grow.
        SOCH - अतंह आर भ: Bridging Divides and Empowering Marginalized Communities

        Driven by a desire to give back to society, the founder of SOCH - अतंह आर भ left her corporate job to pursue her passion for community service. Through initiatives ranging from digital education to gender sensitization, SOCH is addressing multifaceted challenges faced by marginalized communities.

        The organization's Digital Education program aims to bridge the digital divide by providing underprivileged children with access to computer education and vocational training.

        By equipping children with essential digital literacy skills, SOCH is helping them navigate the digital world and pursue opportunities for personal and professional growth.

        In addition to its educational initiatives, SOCH is actively involved in advocacy and awareness-raising efforts for LGBTQ+ rights.

        Through gender sensitization workshops and community outreach programs, the organization strives to promote acceptance, inclusion, and equality for all individuals, regardless of their sexual orientation or gender identity.

        Overall, these women-led NGOs are not only addressing immediate needs but also laying the foundation for long-term societal change.

        Through their visionary leadership, empathy, and commitment, they are transforming lives and building a brighter future for generations to come.

        The Bottom Line

        Women-led NGOs are at the forefront of driving empathy-driven change in society. They are transforming lives, amplifying voices, and building a more equitable world for all.

        As i2u Social Foundation celebrates the impact of these remarkable organizations, let us recognize the invaluable contributions of women leaders in shaping a brighter future for generations to come.

        If you're interested in helping build an equitable society where every child, every woman, every human thrives, reach out to i2u Social Foundation. We'll connect you with verified NGOs to help you invest your time, energy, or money into the humanistic development of society.

        Your just #OneDayForFuture can bring about a lifetime of change for someone.

        Author: Mayurii Rajvanshi

        An avid animal lover with a soft spot for the social sector, Mayurii Rajvanshi is a freelance writer and content specialist on a mission to help brands tell their stories better. She believes powerful storytelling has the potential to change the world for the better."
    </string>

</resources>